A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3 FA388
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Zaire, 1966-1991, n.d.; 709; 31 Box(es)
  - Zaire - Medical Sciences, 709.A
    - Community Systems Foundation - Wilson, Dean, June 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Zaire - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 709.E
    - Badinga Lokenga, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Badinga Lokenga, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Badinga Lokenga, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Badinga Lokenga, December 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Badinga Lokenga, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Badinga Lokenga, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Badinga Lokenga - Supplementary Material (I), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Badinga Lokenga - Supplementary Material (II), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Badinga Lokenga - Supplementary Material (III), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bakonzi Agayo, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Bakonzi Agayo, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bakonzi Agayo, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bakonzi Agayo, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bakonzi Agayo, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bifuko Baharanyi, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bifuko Baharanyi, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bifuko Baharanyi, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Chaponniere, Paulette Alice, 1974-May 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Chaponniere, Paulette Alice, June 1976-1977, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Chizungu Rudahindwa, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Chizungu Rudahindwa, 1975-June 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Chizungu Rudahindwa, July-December 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Chizungu Rudahindwa, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Chizungu Rudahindwa, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Chizungu Rudahindwa, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Futa Mudiumbula, 1973-June 1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Futa Mudiumbula, July 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Futa Mudiumbula, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Futa Mudiumbula, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Ilumbe Itota Nyoka, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Kamoto Ka Yanape Lungunga, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Kamoto Ka Yanape Lungunga, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Kamoto Ka Yanape Lungunga, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Kamoto Ka Yanape Lungunga, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Katwala Ghifem, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Katwala Ghifem, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Katwala Ghifem, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Kayisu Kalenga, 1973-June 1974 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Kayisu Kalenga, July 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Kayisu Kalenga, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Kayisu Kalenga, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Kazadi Mikambile, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Kiatoko Mangeye, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Kazadi Mikambile, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Kiatoko Mangeye, January-June 1974 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Kiatoko Mangeye, July-December 1974 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Kiatoko Mangeye, 1975-July 1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Kiatoko Mangeye, August 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Kiatoko Mangeye, 1978-1979. 1985 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Konde Aena, 1974-July 1976 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Konde Aena, August 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Konde Aena, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Lelo Mamosi Nsilulu, 1973-June 1974 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Lelo Mamosi Nsilulu, July-December 1974 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Lelo Mamosi Nsilulu, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Lema Ki-Munseki, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Lema Ki-Munseki, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Lema Ki-Munseki, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Lema Ki-Munseki, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Mukenge, Leonard, 1966-May 1967 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Mukenge, Leonard, June 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Mukenge, Leonard, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Mukenge, Leonard, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Mukenge, Leonard, 1972-1974, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Mulongoy Kalemani, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Mulongoy Kalemani, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Mushi Mugumorhagerwa, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Mushi Mugumorhagerwa, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Mushi Mugumorhagerwa, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Mushi Mugumorhagerwa, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Mushi Mugumorhagerwa, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Ngay Aben, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Ngay Aben, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Ngay Aben, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Ngay Aben, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, January-October 1979 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, November 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, January-August 1981 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, September 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Ngokwey Ndolamb, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, 1973-May 1974 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, June-August 1974 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, September-December 1974 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, January-June 1975 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, July 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Nsaman Lutu Omgesang, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Nzongola Ntalaja, 1973-June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Nzongola Ntalaja, July 1974-1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Tshilema Tshihiluka, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Tshilema Tshihiluka, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Tshilema Tshihiluka, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Tshilema Tshihiluka, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Tshilema Tshihiluka, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Tshilema Tshihiluka, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Tshimpaka Yanga, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Tshimpaka Yanga, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Tshimpaka Yanga, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Tshimpaka Yanga, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Tshimpe M. Ditumbule, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Tshimpe M. Ditumbule, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Tshimpe M. Ditumbule, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Tshimpe M. Ditumbule, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Tshimpe M. Ditumbule, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Yamvu Makasu a M'Teba, 1973-June 1974 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Yamvu Makasu a M'Teba, July 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Yamvu Makasu a M'Teba, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Yamvu Makasu a M'Teba, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Yamvu Makasu a M'Teba, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Zaire - Social Sciences, 709.S
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science, January-June 1971 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science, July-December 1971 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science, 1972, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - National University of Zaire - Social History, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - National University of Zaire - Social History, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - National University of Zaire - Social History, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Zaire - University Development, 709.UD
    - Minutes, 1972-1981 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - 1970 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - January-October 1971 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - November-December 1971 (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - January-March 1972 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - April 1972 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - May 1972 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - June-November 1972 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - January 1973 (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - February-December 1973 (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - January-May 1975 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - July-December 1975 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - 1978 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - January-May 1979 (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - July 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Supplementary Material (I), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Supplementary Material (II), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Supplementary Material (III), 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Supplementary Material (IV), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Supplementary Material (V), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Supplementary Material (VI), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 151)
    - Administration, January-July 1972 (Box 13, Folder 152)
    - Administration, August-December 1972 (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Administration, January-May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 154)
    - Administration, June-December 1973 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Administration, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 156)
    - Administration, January-May 1975 (Box 13, Folder 157)
    - Administration, June-December 1975 (Box 13, Folder 158)
    - Administration, January-June 1976 (Box 13, Folder 159)
    - Administration, July-December 1976 (Box 13, Folder 160)
    - Administration, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 161)
    - Administration, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 162)
    - Administration, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Administration, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 164)
    - Administration, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    - Agreements, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Agriculture - Consultants, 1971-February 1972 (Box 14, Folder 167)
    - Agriculture - Consultants, March 1972 (Box 14, Folder 168)
    - Agriculture - Consultants, April 1972 (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Agriculture - Consultants, May 1972 (Box 14, Folder 170)
    - Agriculture - Consultants, June-December 1972 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Biomedical Sciences - Consultants, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - Biomedical Sciences - Consultants, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Conferences, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 174)
    - Health Sciences, 1971, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - Health Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - Health Sciences, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 177)
    - Health Sciences, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 178)
    - Health Sciences, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 179)
    - Health Sciences, 1977-1978, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 180)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (I), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (II), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (III), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 183)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (IV), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 184)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (V), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (VI), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (VII), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - Health Sciences - Supplementary Material (VIII), 1980, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 188)
    - National University of Zaire - African Seminar, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 189)
    - National University of Zaire - African Seminar - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 190)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study, January-June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 191)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study, July 1976 (Box 16, Folder 192)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study, August-October 1976 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study, November 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study - Evaluation, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study - Supplementary Material (I), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - National University of Zaire - Agricultural Education Study - Supplementary Material (II), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 197)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 198)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January-September 1972 (Box 17, Folder 199)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, October-November 1972 (Box 17, Folder 200)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, 1973-July 1974 (Box 17, Folder 201)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, August-December 1974 (Box 17, Folder 202)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January-May 1975 (Box 17, Folder 203)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, August-December 1975 (Box 17, Folder 204)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 205)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January 1977 (Box 17, Folder 206)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, February-March 1977 (Box 17, Folder 207)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, April 1977 (Box 17, Folder 208)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, May-July 1977 (Box 17, Folder 209)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, August-September 1977 (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, October-December 1977 (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January-February 1978 (Box 18, Folder 212)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, March-April 1978 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, May-June 1978 (Box 18, Folder 214)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, July 1978 (Box 18, Folder 215)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, August-December 1978 (Box 18, Folder 216)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January-March 1979 (Box 18, Folder 217)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, April-July 1979 (Box 18, Folder 218)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, August 1979 (Box 19, Folder 219)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, September-December 1979 (Box 19, Folder 220)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January-June 1980 (Box 19, Folder 221)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, July-August 1980 (Box 19, Folder 222)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, October-December 1980 (Box 19, Folder 223)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, January-February 1981 (Box 19, Folder 224)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, March-May 1981 (Box 19, Folder 225)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, June 1981 (Box 19, Folder 226)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, July-December 1981 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 228)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture - Supplementary Material (I), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 229)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture - Supplementary Material (II), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 230)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture - Supplementary Material (III), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 231)
    - National University of Zaire - Agriculture - Supplementary Material (IV), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 232)
    - National University of Zaire - Anthropology - Fabian, Johannes, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 233)
    - National University of Zaire - Anthropology - Fabian, Johannes, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 234)
    - National University of Zaire - Anthropology - Schoepf, Brooke G., 1975-August 1976 (Box 20, Folder 235)
    - National University of Zaire - Anthropology - Schoepf, Brooke G., September 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - National University of Zaire - Consultants - Veterinary Medicine, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - National University of Zaire - Consultants - Veterinary Medicine, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - National University of Zaire - Donation of Equipment, 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (I), 1975-1976, 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (II), 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (II), 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (II), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 243)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (II), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 244)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (II), January-June 1981 (Box 21, Folder 245)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics (II), July 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 246)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (I), 1977-1981 (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (II), 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (III), 1978-1981 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (IV), 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (V), [1979] (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (VI), 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (VII), 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (VIII), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (IX), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (X), 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (XI), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (XII), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 259)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (XIII), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 260)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (XIV), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 261)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (XV), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 262)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Supplementary Material (XVI), 1981 (Box 22, Folder 263)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Franck, Peter G., 1973-May 1974 (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Franck, Peter G., June 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics - Franck, Peter G., 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics Books (I), 1974, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics Books (II), 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics Books - Evaluation, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - National University of Zaire - Economics Staff Development, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, January-May 1976 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, June-December 1976 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, January-May 1979 (Box 22, Folder 275)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, June-December 1979 (Box 22, Folder 276)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, January-May 1980 (Box 23, Folder 277)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, May 1980 (Box 23, Folder 278)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, May 1980 (Box 23, Folder 279)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, May 1979 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, June-December 1980 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, January-September 1981 (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, December 1981-May 1982 (Box 23, Folder 283)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, June-August 1982 (Box 23, Folder 284)
    - National University of Zaire - Education, September 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 285)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 286)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (I), 1979 (Box 23, Folder 287)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (II), 1977-1981 (Box 23, Folder 288)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (III), 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 289)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (IV), 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 290)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (V), 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 291)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (VI), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 292)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (VII), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 293)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (VIII), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 294)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (IX), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 295)
    - National University of Zaire - Education - Supplementary Material (X), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 296)
    - National University of Zaire - Educational Colloquium (I), 1974, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 297)
    - National University of Zaire - Educational Colloquium (II), 1974-July 1976 (Box 24, Folder 298)
    - National University of Zaire - Educational Colloquium (II), July 1976 (Box 24, Folder 299)
    - National University of Zaire - Educational Colloquium (III), July-November 1976 (Box 24, Folder 300)
    - National University of Zaire - Educational Colloquium - Evaluation, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 301)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (I), 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 302)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (II), March-May 1974 (Box 24, Folder 303)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (II), June 1974 (Box 24, Folder 304)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (II), July 1974 (Box 24, Folder 305)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (II), August-December 1974 (Box 24, Folder 306)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (II), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 307)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course (II), 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Course - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 309)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Teaching (I), 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 310)
    - National University of Zaire - English Language Teaching (II), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 311)
    - National University of Zaire - History (I), 1974, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 312)
    - National University of Zaire - History (II), 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 313)
    - National University of Zaire - History - Evaluation, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 314)
    - National University of Zaire - History - Jewsiewicki, Bogumil Jacek, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 315)
    - National University of Zaire - International Relations Seminar (I), 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 316)
    - National University of Zaire - International Relations Seminar (II), 1973-January 1974 (Box 25, Folder 317)
    - National University of Zaire - International Relations Seminar (II), February-March 1974 (Box 25, Folder 318)
    - National University of Zaire - International Relations Seminar (II), April 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 319)
    - National University of Zaire - Mining Industry Seminar, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 320)
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science - Gould, David, 1976-February 1977 (Box 25, Folder 321)
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science - Gould, David, March-April 1977 (Box 25, Folder 322)
    - National University of Zaire - Political Science - Gould, David, May-October 1977 (Box 25, Folder 323)